pickzup.com 2013-05-16

# OUR PRIVACY POLICY www.pickzup.com Our Commitment to Your Privacy

                                             OUR PRIVACY POLICY
                                               www.pickzup.com
                                       Our Commitment to Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. Your personal information is kept confidential and secure. To protect your
privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices.
PLEASE READ IT CAREFULLY and should you have any queries, please mail us at support@pickzup.com
                                            Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can place
orders for products and services, make requests, references, play games, earn points, and register to
receive materials. Please note that we are only an online platform providing an opportunity to earn points
and use the same for various proposes. You would be required to create a customer account, if you wish to
purchase recharge coupons and other products and services offered on our website.
The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Full Name, Billing Address (Address, city,
state), Shipping Address, Email ID, Mobile Phone number, Gender, PAN Number (only during Withdrawal
request - money into bank), Bank account number (only during Withdrawal request - money into bank),
Date of Birth, Occupation, Salary Range, Interested Area, Contact list (Used for inviting or contacts
imported from email ID).
We use this information every time you interact and collect points at www.Pickzup.com. You may also
provide such information necessary, if you choose to participate in various activities on the site such as
games, events, posting messages in the comment section or in our forums, sending feedback, entering
contests, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.
Please note that we do not collect financial information directly. The payment options for purchases on the
site are services provided by third party Service providers/Banks/Payment Gateways and you are
transported to their respective websites for the purpose; they use the latest encryption technologies,
password protections, and apply stringent limits on the number of people who have access to your personal
information. Any information provided to them for such purpose, including financial information shall be
governed by the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy of such Service Providers/Payment Gateways and not by
the Terms and Privacy Policy of our site. Please read the said Terms of Use and Privacy Policy before
exercising payment options on our site.
                                            Use of Your Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when registering with Pickzup.com, become a part of
Email campaign, sms campaign, other campaigns, refer others to Pickzup.com, and such other actions which
leads to generating of points/credits.
We do not share this information with third parties except to the extent necessary to confirm an ad-
placement, web analytics etc. By contract, the third parties are required to keep the information
confidential and are not permitted to sell, rent or share your information.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive; the email addresses are not used for any
other purpose provided you have not signed for any Email campaign.
You can also register with our website and if you are a registered user and have agreed our terms of use,
your email ID Will be used for sending ad-mails, account notification and other updates to which you have
expressed your content for receiving the same. Information you provide for the purpose enjoys the same

protection as in the case of information provided for opening an account on our website for placing an
order for any of the products and /or services on the website.
Your personal information may be used for purposes such as survey, contest or others; we will notify you
and give you a chance to opt out before responding to our survey, contest form, or other request.
Additionally, you may choose not to respond or participate in any survey, contest, or other request.
We do not rent, sell, or otherwise provide your personal information to third parties, unless required by
law or by an order of a court of law or tribunal, or deemed necessary for the purpose of enforcing our
‘Terms of Use’ Agreement. All information that you provide will be protected with industry standard
protocols and technology. The collected information will not be sold or given to the Third parties for their
marketing purposes at any cost, but may be used to improve and refine our services and also improve the
design and other aspects of our website.
Our website does not monitor the conduct of its users. We reserve our right to delete, remove or exclude
any listing or information, in our sole discretion, that does not meet our intent, policies or guidelines for the
services offered on our site.
If you do not agree with the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, it may be best to limit your
level of interaction with our site, which could include simply not providing us with personal information.
This privacy policy does not apply to information or comments posted in blogs or sites like Facebook, Orkut
or Twitter etc wherein registered users can post comments and other hyper links which are placed in
Pickzup.com which may lead to a different website.
                                       Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we
have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the
information we collect online. We adopt commercially reasonable procedures and technology designed for
this purpose. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties, including hackers will never
be able to defeat the security measures. But we periodically update and test our technology and systems in
order to improve the protection of customer information. We request you to protect your password by not
sharing it with anyone else, alter your password from time to time, and to take measures to prevent it from
unauthorized access or disclosure.
                                                  Cookies/Links
Our website uses cookies or similar files or scripts to enhance your usage of the site and to support
advanced software functionality to customize our services to your needs.
Our website may contain links to other sites, but we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the
content of such other sites. By including links to other websites, we neither endorse such sites nor certify
the soundness of their data security practices, nor guarantee that the information they contain is accurate
                               How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and correct, update or
remove any information excluding profile name and login name furnished by you at the time of registration
by logging in and visiting My Account page. Alternatively you may send us e-mail at support@Pickzup.com
with the details of your request within a reasonable time limit.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before
granting access or making corrections.

                                          Modification of Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify or change our privacy policies at any time, without prior notice or
information. Hence you may keep yourselves updated for any modifications and/or material changes by
visiting our site periodically. We may also choose to notify users of any material changes and/or
modifications by a putting up a simple notice on the home page of our website.
                                     Dispute-settlement and Governing law
The above policy and the use of customer information shall be governed and interpreted in accordance with
laws of India, without reference to conflict of laws principles. Any disputes arising out of this Policy shall be
referred to an Arbitrator on the panel of Shankar & Shankar Arbitration centre to be mutually agreed upon,
under the provisions of the Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996. The language of Arbitration shall be
English and the venue shall be at Bangalore/Palakkad. All matters arising under this policy shall be subject
to exclusive jurisdiction of courts in Bangalore/Palakkad.
                                                How to contact us
         If you require any clarification or additional information regarding our privacy policy, please contact
us at support@Pickzup.com.
                                                                                                   Management
                                                                                                    Pickzup.com
                                                                                                        THETIST,
                                                                          TARANG BUSINESS PROMOTERS AND
                                                                                             CONSULTANTS LTD
